[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "And what does Michelle think Marilyn's life was really like?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "Michelle", "think", "Marilyn", "'s", "life", "was", "really", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "She created a kind of prison that she couldn't get out of.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "created", "a", "kind", "of", "prison", "that", "she", "could", "n't", "get", "out", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle", "Marilyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "POS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Well, I want -- let's just say I was well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "want", "--", "let", "'s", "just", "say", "I", "was", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", ":", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "-- of something that was done on -- something done on this new fangled technology thing called Tout.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "of", "something", "that", "was", "done", "on", "--", "something", "done", "on", "this", "new", "fangled", "technology", "thing", "called", "Tout", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "You see?", "question_tokens": ["You", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "I don't understand what issue you have with that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "understand", "what", "issue", "you", "have", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meredith Vieira"]}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "What is that about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, precisely for the reasons that that video has just shown me, which is that I should -- the further I am away from Meredith Vieira, the better for my career.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "precisely", "for", "the", "reasons", "that", "that", "video", "has", "just", "shown", "me", ",", "which", "is", "that", "I", "should", "--", "the", "further", "I", "am", "away", "from", "Meredith", "Vieira", ",", "the", "better", "for", "my", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "But I realized then -- I realized it, and I mean this in all sincerity, actually, that you were a -- at heart I saw a brilliant journalist and that's as I suspect how you would like to be seen, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "realized", "then", "--", "I", "realized", "it", ",", "and", "I", "mean", "this", "in", "all", "sincerity", ",", "actually", ",", "that", "you", "were", "a", "--", "at", "heart", "I", "saw", "a", "brilliant", "journalist", "and", "that", "'s", "as", "I", "suspect", "how", "you", "would", "like", "to", "be", "seen", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Well, yes, I would.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "What's it been like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "been", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, you know, it's really weird, Piers, because when I left the \"Today\" show that was my decision.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "weird", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "when", "I", "left", "the", "``", "Today", "''", "show", "that", "was", "my", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Why did you have to get up at 2:30 in the morning because you didn't have to be there until about 5:30?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "have", "to", "get", "up", "at", "2:30", "in", "the", "morning", "because", "you", "did", "n't", "have", "to", "be", "there", "until", "about", "5:30", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "5:00.", "answer_tokens": ["5:00", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["2:30 in the morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Do you feel liberated to have an opinion?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "liberated", "to", "have", "an", "opinion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, I have to be careful because I am part of \"Rock Center\" as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "be", "careful", "because", "I", "am", "part", "of", "``", "Rock", "Center", "''", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Is it Barack Obama being weak as president?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "Barack", "Obama", "being", "weak", "as", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Or is there something just fundamentally inherently wrong the process now that has to be dramatically changed?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "there", "something", "just", "fundamentally", "inherently", "wrong", "the", "process", "now", "that", "has", "to", "be", "dramatically", "changed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I think you would get different answers to that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "would", "get", "different", "answers", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "People that watch the \"Today\" show who lead an often this very normal live well away from all this who must be looking at this in complete -- I would imagine -- increasingly indignant bemusement saying what is happening here to the people supposedly charged with making our lives better?", "question_tokens": ["People", "that", "watch", "the", "``", "Today", "''", "show", "who", "lead", "an", "often", "this", "very", "normal", "live", "well", "away", "from", "all", "this", "who", "must", "be", "looking", "at", "this", "in", "complete", "--", "I", "would", "imagine", "--", "increasingly", "indignant", "bemusement", "saying", "what", "is", "happening", "here", "to", "the", "people", "supposedly", "charged", "with", "making", "our", "lives", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NN", "WP", "NN", "DT", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, I would think that people are truly fed up at this point and they're frustrated and they're hurting because of the economy as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "think", "that", "people", "are", "truly", "fed", "up", "at", "this", "point", "and", "they", "'re", "frustrated", "and", "they", "'re", "hurting", "because", "of", "the", "economy", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What were your emotions like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "your", "emotions", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "It was hard that day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "hard", "that", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What has it been like for you battling most of your adult life knowing that you have this awful condition?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "it", "been", "like", "for", "you", "battling", "most", "of", "your", "adult", "life", "knowing", "that", "you", "have", "this", "awful", "condition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, I've had it for almost 40 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "it", "for", "almost", "40", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Is it very difficult?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "very", "difficult", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, you know, I think you deal with it on a day-to-day basis.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "you", "deal", "with", "it", "on", "a", "day-to-day", "basis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "How have you managed to stay as you appear to be pretty cheery about life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "managed", "to", "stay", "as", "you", "appear", "to", "be", "pretty", "cheery", "about", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, look, it's a -- it's a long road.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "long", "road", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "When did you decide to tell the children that you had multiple sclerosis and how did they react to it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "decide", "to", "tell", "the", "children", "that", "you", "had", "multiple", "sclerosis", "and", "how", "did", "they", "react", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Well, we knew that at some point we were going to have to open up to them and tell them the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "knew", "that", "at", "some", "point", "we", "were", "going", "to", "have", "to", "open", "up", "to", "them", "and", "tell", "them", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Not nearly enough.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "nearly", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Do you know whether they are susceptible to getting this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "whether", "they", "are", "susceptible", "to", "getting", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, we're told that they are no more susceptible than the general population, maybe slightly more susceptible.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "told", "that", "they", "are", "no", "more", "susceptible", "than", "the", "general", "population", ",", "maybe", "slightly", "more", "susceptible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "They couldn't have a better role model than their father?", "question_tokens": ["They", "could", "n't", "have", "a", "better", "role", "model", "than", "their", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do you just enjoy it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "just", "enjoy", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "For all these people who are desperate to be a millionaire, what's it like?", "question_tokens": ["For", "all", "these", "people", "who", "are", "desperate", "to", "be", "a", "millionaire", ",", "what", "'s", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "You tell me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "tell", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PDT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "As somebody who has worked her way up the journalistic ladder, and done it the hard way and with great integrity and so on, how do you feel about the appointment of Chelsea Clinton as an NBC reporter, given that whatever her connections, whatever her background, she clearly hasn't done the journalistic hard yards?", "question_tokens": ["As", "somebody", "who", "has", "worked", "her", "way", "up", "the", "journalistic", "ladder", ",", "and", "done", "it", "the", "hard", "way", "and", "with", "great", "integrity", "and", "so", "on", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "appointment", "of", "Chelsea", "Clinton", "as", "an", "NBC", "reporter", ",", "given", "that", "whatever", "her", "connections", ",", "whatever", "her", "background", ",", "she", "clearly", "has", "n't", "done", "the", "journalistic", "hard", "yards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, people get in for all sorts of reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "people", "get", "in", "for", "all", "sorts", "of", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"], "PERSON": ["Chelsea Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Of all the amazing moments you've experienced as a journalist, Meredith, in your career, if you could relive one again in the next five minutes, if I had that power, what would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "amazing", "moments", "you", "'ve", "experienced", "as", "a", "journalist", ",", "Meredith", ",", "in", "your", "career", ",", "if", "you", "could", "relive", "one", "again", "in", "the", "next", "five", "minutes", ",", "if", "I", "had", "that", "power", ",", "what", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I would -- boy, I've seen a lot of places and I've done a lot of things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "--", "boy", ",", "I", "'ve", "seen", "a", "lot", "of", "places", "and", "I", "'ve", "done", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meredith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What's been the love of a great woman like Meredith in life for you and your life particularly, given the challenges that you've had to face?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "love", "of", "a", "great", "woman", "like", "Meredith", "in", "life", "for", "you", "and", "your", "life", "particularly", ",", "given", "the", "challenges", "that", "you", "'ve", "had", "to", "face", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "She's sitting next to me.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "sitting", "next", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meredith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle"]}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Why Michelle Williams?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "Michelle", "Williams", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Because I've always loved Michelle's work.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'ve", "always", "loved", "Michelle", "'s", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Williams"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "What is the decision making process as a filmmaker in choosing the right kind of person to play somebody so famous?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "decision", "making", "process", "as", "a", "filmmaker", "in", "choosing", "the", "right", "kind", "of", "person", "to", "play", "somebody", "so", "famous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I think there's a lot of ingredients in that decision, if you like.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "ingredients", "in", "that", "decision", ",", "if", "you", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn Monroe"]}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What surprised you most about her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "surprised", "you", "most", "about", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Oh, gosh, I suppose the sort of -- the biggest discovery that I made along the way was that Marilyn Monroe was a character, and that how we commonly think of her, that was a part that she played.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "gosh", ",", "I", "suppose", "the", "sort", "of", "--", "the", "biggest", "discovery", "that", "I", "made", "along", "the", "way", "was", "that", "Marilyn", "Monroe", "was", "a", "character", ",", "and", "that", "how", "we", "commonly", "think", "of", "her", ",", "that", "was", "a", "part", "that", "she", "played", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "How did that happen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "You're just looking for the right man.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "just", "looking", "for", "the", "right", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Do you feel a bit weird when you watch it back there, just how convincing it is?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "a", "bit", "weird", "when", "you", "watch", "it", "back", "there", ",", "just", "how", "convincing", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Oh, gosh, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "gosh", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "JJR", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "ORGAN: Michelle, what did you think of Marilyn as an actress?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Michelle", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "of", "Marilyn", "as", "an", "actress", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I suppose that was one of my other big discoveries along the way, is that, more than anything, she wanted to be a serious actress.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "that", "was", "one", "of", "my", "other", "big", "discoveries", "along", "the", "way", ",", "is", "that", ",", "more", "than", "anything", ",", "she", "wanted", "to", "be", "a", "serious", "actress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle", "Marilyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "So I think after the break, Simon I want to know whether Michelle Williams is equally as big a diva?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "think", "after", "the", "break", ",", "Simon", "I", "want", "to", "know", "whether", "Michelle", "Williams", "is", "equally", "as", "big", "a", "diva", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simon", "Michelle Williams"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Anything else you want to tell us about her?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "else", "you", "want", "to", "tell", "us", "about", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No, I think that's a very good description.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "description", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you like that, or are you very professional about these things?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "like", "that", ",", "or", "are", "you", "very", "professional", "about", "these", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "ILLIAMS: In al honesty, I run ten minutes late every day, everywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLIAMS", ":", "In", "al", "honesty", ",", "I", "run", "ten", "minutes", "late", "every", "day", ",", "everywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "I mean, admit it, Michelle, you must feel sexy when you're playing Marilyn Monroe?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "admit", "it", ",", "Michelle", ",", "you", "must", "feel", "sexy", "when", "you", "'re", "playing", "Marilyn", "Monroe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Honestly, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle", "Marilyn Monroe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Why did you find it so emotional?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "find", "it", "so", "emotional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "You know, it -- I've never spent this long with a character before.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "--", "I", "'ve", "never", "spent", "this", "long", "with", "a", "character", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "How is life for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "life", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "It has a routine.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "has", "a", "routine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "In your big directing debut, you must be excited?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "big", "directing", "debut", ",", "you", "must", "be", "excited", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Very, very excited.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", ",", "very", "excited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]